Hail to the King
Hey!
Aya-chan!
Yo.
You're awfully late.
I was getting tired of waiting.
Yesterday's Best Western Hits.
I recorded it for you.
New songs!
I'm so happy.
Thanks.
The third track is so dope.
It hits you like a knuckle sandwich
in a one-on-one street fight!
I don't think I really get what you mean.
Oh, yeah.
I learned how to sing all the songs
you gave me last time.
No kidding?
Impressive.
Why don't you play?
We can sing together.
Aya-chan?
Hey, Fu...
How about the two of us go pro?
I feel like with you on board, we can make it.
I...
I'm...
The Star of the Next Video is Who?
Okay. Guess that's it.
Mm-hmm.
A nice room with plenty of space.
The question is whether
I can survive living with them.
Let's reach 1,000,000 subs!!
I've gotta do it!
I'll come up with videos
that are sure to go viral!
And to do that...
"Favorite things:"
"Strawberries, dustpans,
long chopsticks, Live-sama,"
"holo stickers, smooth rocks, cosmic peace."
Please fill out this survey
Name: Ichiko
Favorite Things: Strawberries,
dustpans, long chopsticks, Live-sama <3,
holo stickers, smooth rocks, cosmic peace
Skills: Stocks, cleaning, forex,
laundry, cooking
Dumb as a rock.
Huh? Did you say something?
Nope, not a thing.
Strawberries are good, aren't they?
Now for Live...
My favorite thing is the
blood flowing in your veins!
That's all!
Yikes!
I swear...
You want to know more about us
so badly, you printed out surveys?
Nosy, aren't we?
Please fill out this survey
Name:
TOKAGE!!
Favorite Things:
MONEY!!!
Skills:
Yeah, I expected as much.
Huh?
Wasn't there another one of you?
Fu's out at work right now.
What, she has a job?
It's true.
One of our residents is a hard-working girl
who has a real job and pays her rent.
Cut it out. You're making me blush.
I'm not talking about you!
No need to be bashful.
Like hell I am!
Job or no job, I need her
to submit a survey.
Excuse me...
Totally blank.
What's this?
Wait...
Masaki, what are you doing in there?
Live...
I know what our next video's going to be.
Have a good night.
Oh, here she is.
Hey, there!
You two!
How'd you get in here?!
Through the window.
That's trespassing!
Bath thieves!
Hey, don't be such a party pooper.
We're closed for the night.
Okay, okay.
We'll get going, then...
Not!
Allow us to announce our next video.
The star of the next video is you!
The one singing a cover will be Fu!
What?
N-No, thanks.
Eh?
How many times do I have
to tell you I won't do it?
Whew!
Nothing beats a cold one!
Please listen to me!
Why me, anyway?
Because I found out you can sing. Duh.
Wait!
Don't tell me you went in my room!
Whether I did or didn't isn't the issue here.
You love singing, and you used to sing
on the roof all the time, right?
Live told me.
Uh-huh.
You could... hear me?
Now's the time to try
new ideas to rack up the hits!
Videos of song covers are popular,
and there's a good chance
it could gain us subs!
Got it? If you do, then hurry up and—
You're so stubborn!
Masaki-san, you're as stubborn as
the slimy gunk in the bathtubs!
Huh?!
That's one hell of a weird insult!
I'll never sing again.
I don't deserve to.
Sorry.
See ya.
Yeah!
Oh, yeah.
Starting tomorrow, how about
we sing here every day?
Yes, of course!
I'd love to sing with you every day!
If we're gonna be pro singers,
we need to get real!
That's... true.
What's gotten into you?
Having second thoughts about the audition?
No, that's not it!
Then we've gotta buckle down!
Let's kill it.
Y-Yeah.
Bye!
What now?
Thank you for hearing us perform.
You can't be serious.
Yuki-sama...
A pro singer?
Do you plan on being on TV?
As a vampire?
How do you know...
My job is to keep an eye on you lot.
A singer who miraculously doesn't age,
shrouded in mystery,
only making appearances at night...
It'll get people talking, at least.
I know it's a lost cause.
I don't think you do.
Don't cling to a dream
that can never come true.
Gotta tell her...
Gotta tell her.
Gotta tell her!
Open-Air Concert Hall
An outdoor stage...
Shine On! Singing Contest!
I can't back down now.
Not after all this time.
I mean, if I did...
That'd be...
What's up? You okay?
Aya-chan.
Sorry I'm late.
No, it's fine.
Let's make it through.
The two of us.
What's wrong?
Nerves getting to ya?
This is no time to be shaking in your boots!
L-Listen, I...
Aya-chan.
Guess I'm not one to talk.
My folks...
They keep giving me a hard time.
Saying my dream can never come true.
Shut up. What do you know?
I'm banking on this audition.
Wh-Why'd you do that?!
Firing myself up.
F-Firing?!
Next up is entry number 14.
The two-piece act, Who Are You!
Step on up!
Shine On! Singing Contest!
Here we go, Fu!
What am I doing?
I can't even go out in the sunlight!
Fu?
I'm sorry.
Fu!
Damn it!
"Don't deserve to"?
What's that supposed to mean?!
You were singing so happily!
So how come?
I'm back!
Live!
Why are you coming in through the window?
Wait, where'd you go off to?
Here and there for some Fu stuff.
I had an idea of what all this was about,
so I got some answers out of Shige.
Shige... Yuki-san?
All right. Since the song cover
video's riding on this, too,
let's really put our backs into it!
Yeah!
The Folk
All About Folk Songs
New Music
Shine On! Singing Contest!
Singer-Songwriter
Audition
Step up, hotshots! Coming this fall!!!
Will you be the next big TV star?!
Stay Tuned for Updates!
Japanese Folk
& Rock Feature
Live
We're searching for this person!
All info is welcome, so please
leave a comment if you know her.
A Community for
Folk Song Lovers
Mr. Bear
Who is she? Quite the looker
Milk
how old is that photo? lmao
Party of One
I don't know who she is...
Is she a family member?
Akari
She looks tough as nails LOL
Is she one of them delinquent girls??
S.H
who's that? someone famous?
Marguerite
No clue
the sake liker
Never seen her, but I hope
you find her soon <3
Anything?
the sake liker
Never seen her, but I hope
you find her soon <3
Sinji
Whoa, she's awesome!!
Yumi Kimura Smith
I saw her play a concert two years ago.
I think this is the same AYA-san.
Yes!
Um, Masaki-san...
Y-You scared me!
Don't sneak up behind me like that!
I wasn't trying to sneak up on you.
Oh, um, sorry.
You've been acting weird.
Are you up to something?
No way! I wouldn't dream of it!
It's nothing at all!
So long!
Wait right there!
You really suck at telling lies.
I'm not lying.
I can see right through you.
Let me tell you what's up, then.
We went looking for her.
The girl named Aya.
How do you know that name?
We looked it up.
Do you really want me to sing that badly?
So she is the reason why you won't sing.
You're wrong!
It was my own decision not to sing anymore!
Aya-chan's got nothing to do with it!
Why do you keep sticking
your nose in my business?!
I'm doing it for the videos—
No one will enjoy watching me be pressured
into something I don't want to do.
Well...
Please just leave me be.
Fine, then!
Piss and moan until you die, for all I care!
I saw how carefully you kept
those ancient cassettes!
It's obvious that you're still not over her!
We received word of someone named
Aya holding a concert two years ago.
We found the venue location, as well.
Interested?
N-No.
I see.
Then throw it in the trash.
You said you don't deserve to sing.
Just so you know, no one's undeserving
of doing the things they want.
That's all from me.
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
What's up?
Fu left a message!
"I'll be out of the house for a while.
Don't worry about me."
What do we do?
Is it because of all our meddling?
She said not to worry. I'm sure she's fine.
I'm here.
I should have done more research.
My phone stopped working
as soon as I got here, too.
I'm even dumber than Ichiko-chan!
You've had way too much to drink.
I feel sick...
Japanese?
I swear.
E-Excuse me!
Can you tell me how to find this address?
That was a good show, man!
Yeah, we nailed it!
Yeah, let's have a beer!
Excuse me.
Aya-chan performed here.
Sorry, we're closed.
U-Um, I'm...
This case...
Hey, hey, hey!
Hail to the King
Don't touch that!
That guitar's precious to me, y'know.
Hail to the King
Aya-chan's guitar case...
You a friend of Aya or something?
I-I'm Aya-chan's...
Um, English... Um...
You think Fu managed to find Aya-chan?
I'm sure she did!
Good for her, though.
Fu managed to take a bold new step.
Tokage!
Now we might make some cash!
Isn't that just lovely?
Fu!
H-How'd it go?
Aya-chan passed away.
Seriously, human lives are so damn short.
Um, how about some tea?
Ah, I'm fine for now. Thanks for asking.
You're welcome.
Not gonna play it?
After he gave it to you.
I don't know how to.
Aya-chan was always
the one in charge of playing.
Sorry.
I should have looked into it more first.
Let me apologize as well.
You did all of this for me,
but I said those awful things.
No, I did it for the videos.
If I'd acted sooner,
I might have seen her again.
No, if I'd just had the courage
to face her back then...
But I was too scared that she might hate me.
I always make the wrong decision.
Um...
Got a moment?
We found this in the guitar case.
Huh? Is this thing already on?
Sure is. Introduce yourself!
Hey. I'm Aya, a singer.
Great, thanks!
Bring it on!
Today I'm here to interview the Japanese
artist making big, big waves in America!
Is that sarcasm?
No, no.
It'll be true soon enough!
Huh?
Once you make it big, this video
will be worth its weight in gold!
Yeah, yeah.
I'll do my best to make that happen.
Let's get started!
Ask me anything!
In a few words, can you tell us
why you decided to go into singing?
A long time ago, back in my slightly wild era,
there was only one person I was tight with.
I guess it started when I met her.
So she was the one who gave you that push?
Something like that.
Huh...
She was a real killer singer.
If I was with her, we could go pro.
The two of us in the big leagues...
or so I thought.
You thought?
We suddenly lost touch, and that was that.
She ran away from me, without telling me why.
On the day of our audition, at that.
Maybe she had her reasons?
I'm sure she did.
But I wish she'd told me why.
It's seriously a mystery.
I always figured we were real close,
but it turns out there was a lot
I didn't know about her.
Still, I had fun singing together
with her every day.
I bet she... I bet Fu had fun as well.
There's no doubt in my mind about that.
Um, you lost me there.
No surprise.
Well, what I mean is...
If she's out there singing to this day,
that'd make me really happy.
Hey, is that Aya?
Hey, you recording something?
I'm sorry.
For running away by myself.
For disappearing without a word.
For not seeing you
while you were still alive.
I'm sorry!
All I ever wanted was to sing with you.
Aya-chan...
Well?
Not bad for something
we cobbled together, right?
We did all this for you,
so show a little gratitude.
Everyone...
What's gotten into you?!
Just firing myself up.
Okay, all good!
Live-sama, I brought back
souvenirs from New York.
What'd you get?
A wall pennant, a Statue of Liberty
trinket, a t-shirt, bath soaks...
The bath soaks, then!
How nice! You'll be in New Soak City!
Wow.
Next time:
"Blood-or-Die! Desert Island Survival"!
Blood-or-Die! Desert Island Survival
As in, New York City!